[Music]
hello everyone my name is Jamal Thomas I
am your host this is the progressive so
bugs
hope y'all are doing great or I should
say I had a great Mother's Day it is
into Monday at 154 this is technically
so bucks out the dark I think I said
before when I can't sleep and real men
can't sleep they do the news so that's
what I do um the other day acts a basic
question I'm gonna show that video for a
moment but I just want to make this
point but I am NOT the only one that is
asking this particular question a farad
was a blur
for the innocent was popped miss caught
captured indicted and again this is the
third one for the intercept
I don't know when how many years but in
a very short span of time a third person
that has decided to trust the unit's up
with secret information and hand that
information believing that the
government is doing something
mischievous wrong or at the very least
requires some level oversight it's
called I asked I think pretty decently
and the way that typically is this I
have a basic question what is the
intercept doing now I like the other
side Glenn Greenwald is lion Jeremy
scale love those guys what is the
intercept doing a third reporter or
third source whistleblower for the
innocent mr. Scott popped a third source
for the intercept has just been indicted
in this case Daniel hell yeah Daniel
Hale man from Nashville has just been
charged in Alexandria federal court with
leaking classified
nation on the drone warfare program to a
reporter in the details they said the
reporter
sounds like journey scale
now the indictment was pretty specific
yeah it said the intercept when asked
about this essentially said we don't
divulge all sources and these people are
giving us really secret information on a
drone war for a program where they
essentially we have flying killer robots
in of course oversight it one of those a
non-denial denial that ever there
but third source what are you doing
like I don't think I'm wrong an accident
question and I'm saying that is someone
that liked the intercept
I like the penisu now to show that I am
NOT alone in this I mean after all I
just did software engineering and um you
know from a sample formal education
anyway so maybe avidin my interpretation
of this it's maybe not what it seems to
be meaning maybe it doesn't seem like
the intercept as if they're reported
that just that pop that's something in
their process either through
incompetence or intentionality ended up
with people being caught that's what it
seems to be maybe I'm wrong there's
somebody else who also once asked
questions let us look at this just to
show I'm not alone and asking this I'm
not the only one that noticed serious
question for the anisa do you secretly
work for the FBI this is John Kerry Kaku
Jaron Kirk
Kerry Kaku was a whistleblower himself
so that with the prison over the
whistleblowing of the information he
divulged so you can imagine he's
somewhat sensitive to this notion of
whistleblowers going to prison if I hand
you information the information I hand
you I expect a certain degree of safety
in the way that I hate you to
information now I understand that you
can't necessarily perfect this so don't
misunderstand me but three people
getting caught seems pretty high to me
especially for an organization that only
started a few years ago John Karthik ooh
serious question for the intersect do
you secretly work for the FBI David Hale
reality winner and Terry Albury
aww
in prison because of you invented
competence or are you compromised you
owe a lot of people an explanation and
an apology I ask this believe it or not
the last time somebody got caught and I
asked I came to the camera well that
sounds nasty I looked into the camera
and I essentially said as much as I
liked it except to intercept needs to
explain what in their process is
compromised and at the very least are
you evaluating what are your processes
compromised that may be leading to these
people being caught except the last time
the last personal Scott that wasn't that
many months ago and you were again care
Kaku is asking the inflammatory question
or are you compromised like it's one
thing to say are you incompetent that's
understandable from that standpoint are
you confident are you guys [__] ups you
know are you bunglers in regards to
security and ensuring that your source
is not getting caught because if your
source gets caught that's not
necessarily a good thing I mean I can
imagine this does bring attention to it
when these people get caught and get
prosecuted but is that really the
attention that you want to draw to it
don't you want to draw attention to it
back a story itself and by the way this
has to do with the drone warfare program
I'm the person David Hale was working in
this program and he said this program
needed oversight he essentially had a
kill program now Jeremy Scahill released
us in the drone papers man this
information was being able to be matched
up in these people caught Kirk aku goes
further on this and this is the most
inflammatory one yet right here
we shouldn't at all be surprised by it
and it's up blowing his sources take a
look at this what is this
now I've heard this argument peer only
bi in 2009 anybody who publishes stolen
info should help catch the thief now
they're trying to say that the person
who I guess funded the intercept meaning
the seed money for the NS a-- was an
anti whistleblower person and so because
that person was an anti whistleblower
person that the reporters that are
associated with the intercept are
somehow blowing their sources work of it
but that seems outrageous that sounds
entirely outrageous to me an entirely a
nonsense proposition I'm sorry I could
be entirely wrong but Jeremy Scahill
doesn't seem like the person who's gonna
turn his sources over just for shits and
giggles because he's working at the
intersect and I don't see that
which leads kind of another serious
point of is it incompetence is it
possible that all of the people who are
passing these guys information are just
bad at covering their tracks maybe I
don't know what it is but this obscure
person that's popped and carry aku is
asking illegitimate the question when
did you if you guys enjoyed the content
please consider sharing liking this
video or subscribing if you're not
already subscribed and if you definitely
find yourself enjoying this content
please consider supporting the PayPal or
patreon thanks